<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<video_game_reviews>
    <review>
        <title>Baulder's Gate 3</title>
        <rating>9</rating>
        <author>Jenny</author>
        <content>
            "Baulder's Gate 3 was my first ever game like this. i had never really played d&d before either. It honstley was my favorite game of 2023. "
        </content>
    </review>
    <review>
        <title>Elden Ring</title>
        <rating>9.8</rating>
        <author>Ben</author>
        <content> 
            "Elden Ring is a great game.<br>
<br>
I will say that this game is not for everyone's tastes so this is not a complete blanket statement and no one should ever have to defend their dislike of the game for any reason.
<br>
Now the gameplay is what loses most players from playing completely through or even from picking up the game at all. To boil it down the player is building a character for combat and has access to a massive variety of weapons, shields, spells and items to assist you. Every weapon has a moveset for how your character can swing them to harm the enemy and every enemy has a moveset as well for how they will attack you. This leads to the main crux of the gameplay which is to size up the enemy, learn how they operate and how they will come after you and to strategize around killing them before they kill you. 
<br>
Veteran players liken the combat to a dance or a rhythm game as enemies and bosses will likely fall into a pattern and can be predicted if you can practice the flow of the combative dance they show to you. However if you try to fight the flow and go off rhythm or just try to brute force the enemy with no regards to any defense, you will be hurt or killed, these are gods and monsters you are fighting and you are just a person.
<br>
Whether you can conquer this flow or not will determine whether you can enjoy the game. The same as with a standard rhythm game, the joy comes from learning the pattern and flow and mastering the song. The only difference is that the song of this game happens to be a dragon, a 8ft tall abomination with 12 arms or a literal God.
"" 
        </content>
    </review>
    <!-- Add more reviews here -->
</video_game_reviews>
